<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 11:09:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-20.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace admits Black Desert Online is her comfort “guilty pleasure,” mostly played as an idle AFK fishing/selling loop for steady silver and progress—busy-life gaming vibes, no judgment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar looks back at how SWTOR’s Conquest evolved since patch 2.9—early UI, tougher objective scarcity, and that weird housing/guild flagship tie-in shaping how she plays week to week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f8abd39a6afc005f4c16e963f7d05f2f0fa7d744c8e578cfe3c17ede0d594faa.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mailvaltar’s early Diablo II Resurrected: Reign of the Warlock thoughts: no new Act, sure, but the first new class since 2001 feels huge—especially Demon-tree summoning, teleporting minions, and Bind&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5cad68470c02774705336d8e5933577fb2f01790988544aa0fef6c9b726cc390.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Margot’s 3-minute-ish take on Lil Gator Game (played on Switch 2): a cozy, A Short Hike–ish sibling-and-friends adventure with surprisingly Zelda BOTW-like traversal that kept her smiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/6b12e48cf80d2c838cdcd6fb2a2c3f64ecca5f2e8ae1d2c3758499e6babdd22e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sweetie reacts to a Sony patent for a super-thin, all-touchscreen, no-buttons controller (maybe PS6), weighing customizable layouts against accessibility pitfalls, accidental presses, and a potential“&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast pushes north in Dune Awakening into iron-tier crafting, sprints from sandworms, juggles water shortages and shielded bandits, and grumbles at how tightly the main quest forces his building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into Diablo II Resurrected: Reign of the Warlock—new Warlock class, Chronicle collection tracking, and more player-controlled Terror Zones—while side-eyeing Blizzard’s packed release pile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily goes full rant mode on internet age-verification laws, arguing driver’s licenses and face scans wreck privacy and speech while still failing kids—plus real harms like blocking sex-ed and LGBTQ+支&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7f9c98859b88a8b4676749ce0b1f066770e4ec3e6f2a915e1b885b979b0c6033.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Axxuy breaks down the real 2026 price of keeping a personal blog online—domain via Namecheap and self-managed Linode hosting—cheap as hobbies go, but a reminder the web isn’t free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski marks 25 years of “All Your Base Are Belong To Us” by running the original Flash SWF via Ruffle, then swapping in the original MP3 for a higher-fidelity remaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer riffs on Obama at the NBA All-Star game, ATProto vs RSS-land Markdown/HTML/OPML handling, the “podcasting is closed” YouTube panic, and remembering Aldus Pagemaker’s impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 20 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae reflects on boredom as almost physical pain, ADHD vibes, and how books, diaries, fanfic, LiveJournal roleplay, and early school broadband shaped their reading/writing (and probably kept them&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-20.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-19.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace listens in on her first Signal Cartel leadership fireside in EVE Online—warm jokes, real stats, and a tantalizing, still-redacted future for Anoikis Division recruitment that leaves her both&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp cheers LOTRO Update 46.1’s global UI scaling, laughs at a quest that literally tells you to stop trying to tame a young elephant, and grinds through overtuned high-HP mobs on the way to level 160.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa digs into Tunnels &amp; Trolls: A New Age’s quickstart—new stats, no classes, renamed spells, and altered combat—and worries the redesign sands off the quirky charm that made T&amp;T special.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux is rebooting EVE Blog Banter as The New Eden Banter: monthly prompts, link roundups, and a “be cool” rule—basically bringing blog-hopping New Eden vibes back in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss nears Baldur’s Gate 3’s final battle with dread, calling out late-game chaos and a camera that fights you (hello z-axis), plus a haunted multi-floor house that forced reload city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast’s “Sibling Time” pivots from a Destiny Rising slump to Dune Awakening prep (yes, a sandbike booster seat) and an Enshrouded return—plus the classic struggle of joining co-op while “offline.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm’s Guild Wars crew hits Yak’s Bend feeling buff with new henchmen, then learns overland scaling and squishy melee buddies mean wipes, penalties, and very whiny escort “helpers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner compares today’s AI rush to past crazes like vaping, legalization, and netbooks, arguing we’re still in the messy tinkering phase—like smart homes—while hype swings between utopia and doom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/3ea0a516c0d87e282ad12bbfc8791eb3c5547d48b6122c839af973d0b3cfd705.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar reflects on leaving a long job and sorting what actually transfers: credentials vs skills, contacts vs real network, and why what you can do matters more than titles, authority, or org charts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier flags AISLE’s AI finding 12 OpenSSL zero-days (and even proposing patches), underscoring how AI-driven vuln discovery is accelerating—and how both attackers and defenders will use it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer starts a new Twitter account and riffs on RSS-world confusion after a Spurlock feed reader launch, including accidentally congratulating the wrong Spurlock and musing about FeedLand/OPML.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 19 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold uses board game AI drama to skewer exec fantasies: cites the Remote Labor Index’s low LLM success rates, warns progress may slow, and argues “few dollars a day” pricing is honeymoon-phase myth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-19.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-18.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/768e19990855ce3e7fd5ac4bfc0bc32f0daddc1816be8e2955b472d78b064e3c.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexia rounds up eight cozy 2026 games she’s hyped for, from Solarpunk’s co-op crafting to Nivalis’ cyberpunk management and Witchbrook’s magical school life (with some demos to try now).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp swaps his World of Warcraft Midnight main from Death Knight to a stress-free Gnome Warlock, then fills the lull with endeavors, delves, and slowly furnishing a bookshop café.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa digs into The Fellowship of the Ring on PS2, a book-faithful oddball that actually includes Tom Bombadil and Barrow-wights, plus Ring invisibility with a risky purity meter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/b6b344a1f8da7a7f4a6009dad54db841590eed3dca425afcd89d0e8ebec59e67.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nimgimli admits daily login rewards and battle passes quietly turn live-service games into a checklist—especially once you pay—until “just knock out the dailies” replaces actually playing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/00a271d2893a22838427a2ae57d461aabec3783c448be225e736a6b9a9d667c3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar preps for World of Warcraft: Midnight with lighter expectations—until he admits he’ll still clean bags, clear quest logs, and log into all 53 alts for rested XP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast returns to Dune Awakening on a reactivated private server, rerolls Swordmaster for survivability, plays more efficiently after learning the early-game flow, and keeps base-building practical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm breaks down why Imperium attention is locked on TEST’s Keepstar armor timer in Atioth, with null-sec history, Pandemic Horde’s collapse, and “why are you here?” drama baked in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5eab042fa5f26dc78cd61970dacb37f229e43eb745dc89b71838f854799eddcc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghastly spotlights the “No Ice In Minnesota” Itch.io charity bundle supporting the Immigrant Law Center of Minnesota, with dozens of games/tools/books for $10 and availability through March 13.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f0059d27315e1b199d6d67be9b2f27f0212da08fbb262a6db2ee17875f60450e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;WCRobinson says Capcom’s 20-minute Pragmata demo on Switch 2 sold them on the RE Engine sci-fi vibe, Hugh-and-android-Diana setup, and combat/exploration ahead of its April 24 release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss gleefully shares Lana Del Rey’s “White Feather Hawk Tail Deer Hunter,” along with a YouTube commenter’s quick-and-dirty lyrics, because waiting ten months is too long to keep quiet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer vents about broken FedEx/DHL shipping sites, argues for AI-upgraded UX, floats pay-per-article paywalls, and laments Twitter’s locked-down mess and account woes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 18 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger tallies what it actually costs to keep a personal blog running in 2026—domain + privacy and Squarespace hosting—landing at about £187/year for the privilege of owning your words.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-18.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/907d0e06534fcd206c847a182352b79b51b35cc38d28937dfc80ec43bacf6a38.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Azuriel spotlights Claire Obscur: Expedition 33’s Picto system—Materia-like passives, Luma point-buy, and juicy synergies—and uses it to dunk on “customization” in The Outer Worlds 2 and Avowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi revisits The Chaos Engine’s Bitmap Brothers swagger, from co-op that makes you compete for loot to a “sorry” box-note password change—annoying, sure, but it looks and sounds gorgeous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista says Under The Island nails that Saturday-morning-kid nostalgia, sending heroine Nia (and reluctant ally Avocado) across Seashell Island’s biomes, puzzles, dungeons, and monsters to stop it’s-s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna teams up with eight writers to reflect on 2025 gaming habits—buying fewer hype recs, getting better at reading trailers, leaning on solid character writing, and finally making peace with demos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar reacts to WoW’s Midnight pre-patch “ability pruning,” finding Prot Warrior mostly fine but Holy Priest gutted (goodbye Shield, Renew, Mind Blast), and worries the simplification makes some DPS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie explains why the familiar LEGO formula still hits for her, tying LEGO Pirates of the Caribbean to comfort-gaming and her complicated history with completionism (plus there’s a podcast version).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm jumps into No Man’s Sky Expedition 21: Remnant after patches land, runs into contradictory expedition messaging, and discovers the new planetary garbage/waste-removal twist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/963329a291b16c942e6e2e48d83f9b7df8d195b72a62616ba711448d655177fe.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friendly Necromancer takes a $10 gamble on Quinfall, praising the surprisingly deep character creator while side-eyeing the wonky VO lore and familiar MMO mashup vibes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss riffs on running out of blog ideas, detours into a newly surfaced early Talking Heads demo, and admits he needs a steady drip of new music to stay engaged—even with all-time favorites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast drops a new Mixtape Mondays entry inspired by friend Mallow’s playlist, anchoring a 15-song mood around how Nick Cave, PJ Harvey, and She Wants Revenge flow together just right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier argues “prompt injection” is just step one, proposing a seven-stage “promptware kill chain” for LLM attacks—especially nasty indirect injections via retrieved web/email/docs (even image&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer says his Twitter/X account got hijacked and asks for it to be shut down, then cheers a new micro.blog RSS “mentions” feed from Manton Reece as web-by-RSS working right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-17.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-16.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa dives into HeroQuest First Light’s King Forgrin’s Trove—spy trouble, Dread Warriors and Abominations, a trap-fired room, and a loot haul to prep for the campaign’s final battles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/fe42e011903d89462478749d0e0bc0c074ddc1fcc05c1a8dac35457669c9e0cb.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cliffski shows off Ridiculous Space Battles’ slick new race-selection animation and a calmer deployment screen palette, then tees up the next grind: weapon/module balance via fast battle-sim stats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar republishes (with updates and permission) FJ Brodie’s SWTOR Hoth GSI missions guide—where to grab terminals, quick-slot Seeker Droid/Macrobinoculars, and run dailies like Crash Courses post-7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm checks in on Fantasy Critic League week seven as six games finally hit the board—Mewgenics lands strong, while a few sub-80 launches flirt with the regret zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael drops a packed gaming-blog roundup—newsletters, indie dev blogs, ttrpg Bloggies nominees, Bitsy’s creator doing Twine-for-Casio IF, Zork troll combat, festival culture worries, and cheap minis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae’s week 7 digest covers settling into CachyOS, a new job offer and paperwork, plus recent Mrs Bradley mysteries—highlighting The Devil at Saxon Wall as a top recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a77cddcecfc61fbf8bf86d890608ebec7f9e53c1914abd9655fbfee615c2fb59.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juhis describes bizarre “wake up early” dreams where he has to finish video-game-style tasks before waking, stuck in a looping Groundhog Day vibe—this time he escaped in time for the doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold digs into board-game YouTube ad drama, arguing paid view-boosting and algorithm gaming can juice numbers without real buyers—great for dashboards, useless for selling actual consumer goods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush traces discovering Jennifer Government via NationStates, resurrects a long-lost “Republic of Bauhinia,” and shares its hilariously bleak autogenerated profile—consumerism, vanishing dissent,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a90620097624cae57edb193379e4a70f87b34096acc7c5d0b07d957b947a3e22.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Bray shares calm, no-polemics anecdata: Rob Sayre used Claude while sending PRs to Quamina, a Go JSON-matching library, and the merged changes roughly doubled benchmark speed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer asks for help fixing Daytona search “NaN” archive glitches via GitHub issues, then wishes micro.blog offered a comments feed so replies on his cross-posted linkblog don’t vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ac498263c07a3920e96459f262f0ccd30c02447d27bdae5229beff3f7568c007.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockade85 unpacks a self-destructive need to be “top of the heap,” from work metrics to Ohio State football and co-op games like FFXIV and Helldivers 2—always fearing he’s not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-16.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
