<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 11:50:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-17.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/907d0e06534fcd206c847a182352b79b51b35cc38d28937dfc80ec43bacf6a38.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Azuriel spotlights Claire Obscur: Expedition 33’s Picto system—Materia-like passives, Luma point-buy, and juicy synergies—and uses it to dunk on “customization” in The Outer Worlds 2 and Avowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi revisits The Chaos Engine’s Bitmap Brothers swagger, from co-op that makes you compete for loot to a “sorry” box-note password change—annoying, sure, but it looks and sounds gorgeous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista says Under The Island nails that Saturday-morning-kid nostalgia, sending heroine Nia (and reluctant ally Avocado) across Seashell Island’s biomes, puzzles, dungeons, and monsters to stop it’s-s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna teams up with eight writers to reflect on 2025 gaming habits—buying fewer hype recs, getting better at reading trailers, leaning on solid character writing, and finally making peace with demos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar reacts to WoW’s Midnight pre-patch “ability pruning,” finding Prot Warrior mostly fine but Holy Priest gutted (goodbye Shield, Renew, Mind Blast), and worries the simplification makes some DPS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie explains why the familiar LEGO formula still hits for her, tying LEGO Pirates of the Caribbean to comfort-gaming and her complicated history with completionism (plus there’s a podcast version).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm jumps into No Man’s Sky Expedition 21: Remnant after patches land, runs into contradictory expedition messaging, and discovers the new planetary garbage/waste-removal twist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/963329a291b16c942e6e2e48d83f9b7df8d195b72a62616ba711448d655177fe.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friendly Necromancer takes a $10 gamble on Quinfall, praising the surprisingly deep character creator while side-eyeing the wonky VO lore and familiar MMO mashup vibes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss riffs on running out of blog ideas, detours into a newly surfaced early Talking Heads demo, and admits he needs a steady drip of new music to stay engaged—even with all-time favorites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast drops a new Mixtape Mondays entry inspired by friend Mallow’s playlist, anchoring a 15-song mood around how Nick Cave, PJ Harvey, and She Wants Revenge flow together just right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier argues “prompt injection” is just step one, proposing a seven-stage “promptware kill chain” for LLM attacks—especially nasty indirect injections via retrieved web/email/docs (even image&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 17 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer says his Twitter/X account got hijacked and asks for it to be shut down, then cheers a new micro.blog RSS “mentions” feed from Manton Reece as web-by-RSS working right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-17.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-16.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa dives into HeroQuest First Light’s King Forgrin’s Trove—spy trouble, Dread Warriors and Abominations, a trap-fired room, and a loot haul to prep for the campaign’s final battles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/fe42e011903d89462478749d0e0bc0c074ddc1fcc05c1a8dac35457669c9e0cb.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cliffski shows off Ridiculous Space Battles’ slick new race-selection animation and a calmer deployment screen palette, then tees up the next grind: weapon/module balance via fast battle-sim stats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar republishes (with updates and permission) FJ Brodie’s SWTOR Hoth GSI missions guide—where to grab terminals, quick-slot Seeker Droid/Macrobinoculars, and run dailies like Crash Courses post-7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm checks in on Fantasy Critic League week seven as six games finally hit the board—Mewgenics lands strong, while a few sub-80 launches flirt with the regret zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael drops a packed gaming-blog roundup—newsletters, indie dev blogs, ttrpg Bloggies nominees, Bitsy’s creator doing Twine-for-Casio IF, Zork troll combat, festival culture worries, and cheap minis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae’s week 7 digest covers settling into CachyOS, a new job offer and paperwork, plus recent Mrs Bradley mysteries—highlighting The Devil at Saxon Wall as a top recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a77cddcecfc61fbf8bf86d890608ebec7f9e53c1914abd9655fbfee615c2fb59.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juhis describes bizarre “wake up early” dreams where he has to finish video-game-style tasks before waking, stuck in a looping Groundhog Day vibe—this time he escaped in time for the doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold digs into board-game YouTube ad drama, arguing paid view-boosting and algorithm gaming can juice numbers without real buyers—great for dashboards, useless for selling actual consumer goods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush traces discovering Jennifer Government via NationStates, resurrects a long-lost “Republic of Bauhinia,” and shares its hilariously bleak autogenerated profile—consumerism, vanishing dissent,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a90620097624cae57edb193379e4a70f87b34096acc7c5d0b07d957b947a3e22.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Bray shares calm, no-polemics anecdata: Rob Sayre used Claude while sending PRs to Quamina, a Go JSON-matching library, and the merged changes roughly doubled benchmark speed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer asks for help fixing Daytona search “NaN” archive glitches via GitHub issues, then wishes micro.blog offered a comments feed so replies on his cross-posted linkblog don’t vanish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ac498263c07a3920e96459f262f0ccd30c02447d27bdae5229beff3f7568c007.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 16 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockade85 unpacks a self-destructive need to be “top of the heap,” from work metrics to Ohio State football and co-op games like FFXIV and Helldivers 2—always fearing he’s not good enough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-16.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss reacts to Playable Worlds layoffs on Stars Reach, pointing out it’s still pre-alpha and that trimming the only-game studio this early feels like a serious warning sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7ca8850a216c596b9fa7946ac5d978c12a6d9ab6d182767e9f85f99126d85f44.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole rants about misinformation after trying to look up Phantasy Star Fukkokuban (a Master System game packaged in a Genesis cart), and getting sketchy-seeming search results alongside stalwarts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar skips the Account Played addon but still totals her WoW /played time, sharing a top-five list where her original 2007 character dwarfs the rest and a MoP Classic hunter surprisingly hits #2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast tries Diablo II’s surprise Warlock class (shadow-dropped and feeling hilariously overpowered), notes it’s coming to Diablo IV and Diablo Immortal too, and checks out Destiny Rising’s LunarNew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into Playable World’s “reorganization” (read: layoffs) on Stars Reach, noting the classic Friday-after-4pm timing and the uneasy déjà vu of MMO staffing cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin didn’t hit the $500/month Patreon goal, but he’s building Zork 3 anyway—bare-bones build already running, with plans to finish Zork 3, Deadline, and Starcross by May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger spotlights London’s British Optical Association Museum—a charming Georgian-house “hidden gem” with a witty curator-led optometry history tour, from old signage to a Harry Potter glasses display.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski riffs on the SF blackout hearing: PG&amp;E says the mayor requested power for the War Memorial Opera House, then later calls it a “misunderstanding,” and JWZ wonders why PG&amp;E would do him&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner rounds up a Sunday reading list about staying aware amid “something big” (AI), plus essays on art, social “rewilding,” screenless tech skepticism, nuance, surveillance, winter firewood demand,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae lists their daily-driver setup after moving from Windows 11 to CachyOS (KDE Plasma 6/Wayland), sticking with Firefox for everyday browsing and using Brave for DRM-heavy streaming sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier posts his upcoming speaking calendar—Ontario Tech, Personal AI Summit, WSJ Tech Live: Cybersecurity, the Ross Anderson Lecture at Cambridge, and RSAC 2026—so you can catch him live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer vents about browsers hiding RSS feeds, “tiny-little-text-box” social apps that break the Back button, and even suggests AIs should take a run at Wikipedia’s errors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-15.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-14.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp remodels his World of Warcraft house room-by-room, juggles prepatch world-boss grind and transmog tinkering, and recruits his daughter to help build a cozy ’90s coffeehouse/bookstore alt-café.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa checks out Othello Trigger, a Chrono Trigger riff that’s mostly Othello, and nerds out over cramming characters, screens, and discs into tiny Game Boy Color memory via GB Studio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi dives into the 2000 PC Legend of the Sacred Stone tie-in, praising its action-RPG simplicity, mouse-driven combat rhythm, and gnarly payoffs like decapitations and fiery magic explosions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f8abd39a6afc005f4c16e963f7d05f2f0fa7d744c8e578cfe3c17ede0d594faa.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mailvaltar can’t believe Diablo II: Resurrected actually got an expansion—new class, items/runewords, endgame, loot filter, and currency stash tabs—then curses being too sick to play yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm runs Friday-the-13th bullet points on gamers hating gen-AI “slop” (survey stats and all) and Discord’s looming age verification pitch—government IDs, backlash, and “we’ll use AI” reassurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael’s indie roundup plugs the No ICE in Minnesota Itch bundle, gushes over Africanfuturist heist game Relooted, celebrates doodle-racer Gradient.horse, and notes new/renewed adventure games and B&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss dusts off the listening diary with 13 Friday-the-13th picks, shouting out videos like A$AP Rocky’s “Punk Rocky” and digging into synth/glam-punk-ish vibes with plenty of side commentary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski drops a Valentine’s-adjacent “previously” link chain—a greatest-hits trail of past oddities and Xscreensaver-adjacent posts to click around and lose an afternoon to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae shares a no-frills desk setup and a rant about “best of” gamer gear elitism, spotlighting practical picks like an 8BitDo Lite 2 controller and a thrifted 27" 1080p monitor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker tears into a NYT-reported Meta memo about facial recognition in smart glasses, warning about privacy harms, “dynamic political environment” timing, and creepy real-world misuse already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer argues news should become a distributed, unownable, replaceable system (with AI QA overseen by a nonprofit of retired journalists), then raves about Anker open-ear earbuds being weirdly, aw&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/16604299853e3ae7ab27193684e1c47e2a699e21ffea237c029ffd7fc3374aac.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JJM wires up a day-friendly light theme toggle across Neovim, tmux, and wezterm via a custom :ToggleLights command, some Lua, and a marker-file hack because wezterm won’t cooperate remotely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-14.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-13.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren reviews Flufftopia: Fluffmazing Edition—cute piggy-bank clicker town-building that runs fine on Steam Deck (tiny UI caveats), then quietly hints at a clever, darker twist and multiple endings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp talks about hitting an “ebb” in LOTRO—logging in more from duty than excitement—so he’s keeping play light until the spark returns, while enjoying touches like adorable elephants and the Grey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux gets parachuted into a Fallout TTRPG set in a brutal Boston winter and rolls up a Mister Handy with a sketchy “security update,” joining a Vault pedicurist, scavenger, and lucid ghoul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista celebrates Starsand Island hitting Steam Early Access/Xbox Preview, pitching its cozy life-sim mix of farming, fishing, animal care, exploration, romance, and island mysteries—with community-sh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/51c04925b679dacd0ef9aa40f9c4598d64613840613c00e2dc4c20ddf92463b7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pixel One vents about a live-service edge case: a paid character transfer token fails, support follows the script, then closes the ticket as “resolved” anyway—KPI theater over fixing the block.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/e853d6a4ed4654210b61c733cf9990dc7182a8fb9040b7b14f2222c9a2ba934f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;RPG Codex flags that Sector Unknown is out, slotting it into their rapid-fire headline stream of RPG releases and announcements for anyone tracking what’s newly shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into No Man’s Sky Update 6.2 “Remnant,” where the Colossus exocraft gets serious customization plus scrap-world industrial waste collecting and Waste Processing Plants to toot at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5eab042fa5f26dc78cd61970dacb37f229e43eb745dc89b71838f854799eddcc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghastly’s fed up with GOG’s generative-AI promo stance and points to DRM-free alternatives like zoom-platform and Fire Flower Games, plus preservation-minded exoDOS for old DOS titles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger lays out a UK household’s monthly budget reality—council tax, utilities, travel, groceries, housing—and why inflation and annual April price hikes make cutting costs feel like a grim puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski marvels that you can effectively DoS a Waymo by leaving its door open, and dunks on the fix: paying DoorDash drivers about $10 to go close it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier breaks down a New York proposal to add “blocking technology” to 3D printers that scans every file for firearm blueprints, arguing it’s DRM-style policy that won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer asks Docker-capable folks to test FeedLand’s new easier setup and help bootstrap the “feediverse,” then riffs on AI intelligence debates and a ChatGPT “it listens” anecdote.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-13.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
