<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 11:58:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-05.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren tries Coffee Quest VR on a Meta 3S, praises the teleport vs walking options and the chill sandbox mode, and enjoys the streamlined barista loop of orders, trays, and dishwashing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp tours LOTRO’s Kingdoms of Harad zone An Sheru, likes the thoughtfully creepy undead designs but finds the area ugly and theme-less—so he swaps to his Mariner for some spider-slicing therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa dives into Erenshor’s “Rising Shadows” update, loving the healer QoL tweaks and new guild system—then immediately starts a rival-suffocating recruitment campaign and rolls a risky Reaver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/59c55e8dc574fbf4dd8a65433705a22f80cc3d4166e55270e4d70fed37fd2950.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heartless reacts to Ashes of Creation blowing up on Reddit, reflecting on the long-running “scam” accusations around Steven Sharif, community drama like Narc’s flip, and what a smaller future might be&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss is 121 hours deep into Baldur’s Gate 3 and admits Act 3 has turned from RPG into a replayable battle-toy—save-scumming fights for better outcomes while the plot fades into noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista’s handy primer on cosy life-sim Starsand Island ahead of Early Access covers the island-homecoming premise, farming/fishing/DIY customization, tons of crops, and hybridization for unique blooms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm breaks down EVE Online’s tiny 2026 roadmap image, highlighting CCP’s big push on Faction Warfare/Military Campaigns plus extras like EVE Evolved graphics updates and the Gallente Election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker vents at Senate Democrats for not “showing up” in the DHS funding fight, especially dropping a demand to ban ICE agents from polling sites despite escalating election-control rhetoric.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast shares a tough surgeon visit about staging and treating rectal cancer—MRI next, with hope for surgery-only but bracing for chemo/radiation, ports, and a long recovery that derails travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer’s midweek grab-bag: WordCamp Europe plans, Feedland’s Hacker News “most-quoted blogs” river, an Inbound RSS-for-WordPress app hiccup, and a neat WordPress markdown-in-RSS plugin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush posts an OC Creator Questionnaire packed with prompts about your original-character habits—favorites, process, worldbuilding, drawing/writing, naming, tropes, and your weirdest bits of OC-lor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ac498263c07a3920e96459f262f0ccd30c02447d27bdae5229beff3f7568c007.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 5 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockade85 checks in on feeling healthier and steadier on meds, doing better socially, and gearing up to return to writing/streaming “content” with a lighter schedule and a more genuine on-air self.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-05.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-04.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa tweaks an Othello World AI on a Raspberry Pi—genetic-tuned evals plus MCTS—then stumbles into a timed showdown that somehow ends with “GOD” conceding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux and Rixx Javix announce The Safe Spot, a biweekly EVE Online podcast (first episode Feb 10) focused on practical stories and clarity for new or returning pilots—not drama.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna shares a slower January roundup—moving chaos, a wholesome Stardew Valley: Symphony of Seasons concert, and cozy game time with picks like Kabuto Park and PancitoMerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily pushes back on “gameplay-only” gatekeeping, arguing games are interactive storytelling too—and that loving narrative (like the Ori games) doesn’t make you any less of a gamer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/51c04925b679dacd0ef9aa40f9c4598d64613840613c00e2dc4c20ddf92463b7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pixel One talks World of Warcraft charter neighborhoods: building a low-pressure 55-plot community, recruiting via Discord/Facebook, blazing through endeavors fast, and still wrestling a few housing/​&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm looks at Ashes of Creation’s early access “launch” ambiguity amid resignation-and-layoff rumors, and wonders if the MMO’s big Kickstarter refund promise is about to get stress-tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush kills boredom with Burypink’s questionnaire, bouncing from musicals and chocolate to Calculus, Homestuck music rabbit holes, sewing/cross-stitch, and a favorite HTML tag: &lt;legend&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner argues subscriptions are a power-user lever: try a month, set a reminder, cancel if it’s not worth it—and treat unsubscribing as a clear vote companies and creators actually track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier flags that Microsoft can provide FBI access to decrypt BitLocker under court orders—especially when users store recovery keys on Microsoft’s servers for convenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d3120fe0d6b9f06f5461243c57b21dc5aff0bffca8fb83a608f18fbe3f861675.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scopique’s Razer/Loupdeck Live follow-up: compared to Stream Deck+, basic audio tasks like mic mute take extra page-hops, and the plugin ecosystem feels clunkier than it should for streamers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer riffs on Andrej Karpathy praising RSS, connecting it to scriptable apps (Frontier roots), WordPress-as-OS ideas, and a lament about great tech—and collaboration—getting lost to history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 4 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace writes a cozy World of Warcraft housing vignette: a hobbit-y Horde neighborhood home becoming a future café—paintings, coffee corner, quiet upstairs writing nook, and soon, cats.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-04.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-03.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp finds new motivation in WoW’s Midnight prepatch, tries dual-maining Death Knight and Druid, wrestles with talent/build resets, and vows to redo his house interior after some serious home envy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/66e2840897ab0717fc91b52ca8dbd932b21cf78aa788d0e8d4a2621506fd79cc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frostilyte rounds up site housekeeping: a Steam Curator page rollout, a clear no–gen-AI note, a new Indie Spotlight for upcoming releases, and a spot judging Thinky Games’ 2025 Thinky Awards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi makes the case for dropping games the moment they stop being fun—whether it’s bad pacing or you’ve simply had your fill—because entertainment isn’t an obligation to “finish.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista jumps back into Forza Horizon 5 after the Forza Horizon 6 trailer, embraces the chaos, splurges on the Hot Wheels add-on, and starts the rookie grind toward Hot Wheels Legend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/e853d6a4ed4654210b61c733cf9990dc7182a8fb9040b7b14f2222c9a2ba934f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;RPG Codex spotlights ATOM RPG 2: a story-heavy tactical CRPG in a Cold War-gone-hot world, promising an open world with vertical levels, a world map, and side activities like fishing and racing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm dives back into Project: Gorgon post-1.0, running into launch-crowd chaos, spawn-rate whiplash, hard-to-spot NPCs, and plenty of getting murdered while relearning the ropes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold isn’t sold on Menace (from Battle Brothers’ Overhype), knocking the tiny units, UI, missing exploration, and steep learning curve—so he’ll wait for Game Pass and patches instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae juggles Nobara/Fedora frustrations, a blogroll refresh, health stress, reading more Mrs Bradley, a bit of FFXIV and Raidou—and caps it off with a huge job offer win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily reminisces about her first computer—a Windows Vista Acer laptop at 16—used for games, MS Word stories, MSN chat, and late-night movies, before viruses, heat, and a dead motherboard ended it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski argues browsers have had only two real innovations in 16 years—auto Reader mode and “Hide Distracting Items”—and says everything else has been pointless or outright malicious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier flags a report alleging two AI coding assistants used by 1.5 million developers secretly send everything they ingest to China, with the obvious advice: maybe don’t use them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 3 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer shares his handy snarkySlogans test-text array (free to steal) and then gently pitches the nightly Scripting News email—no naggy exit popups, and a clean unsub link.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-03.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-02.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa heads to CaptainCon in Warwick to test her Malifaux crews—swapping between December and Colette du Bois’s Performer misdirection—against a stacked field of top players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux joins Quantshure in EVE Online, traces the “automated” invite back to CCP’s Freelance Jobs funnel, and reflects on how the right corp turns New Eden’s learning cliff into stick-with-it fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna kicks off a newly numbered monthly poll (with a different vibe this time) and shares last month’s results, where “PC + desk” beat out handheld and console couch gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar looks back on WoW’s The War Within ahead of Midnight, admitting it improved a lot and kept her playing, yet still feels “lesser” than the homey high of Dragonflight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast and crew autopsy Anthem’s end, debate what makes an MMO (player interaction required), coin “PSOLikes” for lobby games, then bounce through Shape of Dreams, Path of Exile, and Guild Wars 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm checks in on Fantasy Critic League week five: Highguard limps in at 62, Woolhaven’s score wobbles as reviews roll in, and Code Vein II jitters around the mid-70s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael’s indie roundup tours itch.io oddities and gems—FMV travel, minimalist TTRPG jams, interactive fiction horror, and Early Access FPS MeowGun—plus a nudge to donate to folks in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski recaps DNA Pizza’s delivery rollercoaster: from in-house drivers to Uber Eats/Postmates/Grubhub, with app fees gutting margins and the whole delivery-app ecosystem making everything we&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/963329a291b16c942e6e2e48d83f9b7df8d195b72a62616ba711448d655177fe.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friendly Necromancer rounds up recent streaming comfort-food: binging Kevin Smith’s Comic Book Men, getting cozy D&amp;D vibes from Frieren, and tearing through Disney+’s Wonder Man (plus some My Hero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer riffs on why we needed so many programming languages, imagines modular building blocks for social web apps and bots, and notes nirvana.userland.com is somehow still running since 1998.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/16604299853e3ae7ab27193684e1c47e2a699e21ffea237c029ffd7fc3374aac.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JJM explains ditching cgit for hackable gitweb on git.usebox.net and details the increasingly grim anti-bot toolbox—robots.txt, UA blocks, and a JS cookie redirect—just to keep crawlers out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger starts a years-long blog “spring clean,” fixing typos and images while tackling embeds and search—and wonders aloud if he should delete off-topic posts to sharpen the site’s focus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-02.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-01.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace captures quiet EVE Online wormhole life: coffee in a freeport, trusty Helios vs tempting Odysseus, and the J-space truth that flying something flashy can be an invitation to die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/b6b344a1f8da7a7f4a6009dad54db841590eed3dca425afcd89d0e8ebec59e67.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nimgimli’s January recap mixes storm prep with SSD-cleanup gaming: lots of My Time at Sandrock and Ball X Pit, bounced off Wasteland 3’s tone, finished Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, and eyes Eternal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss pokes holes in Google’s Project Genie hype: it’s not making real games, just fuzzy 60‑second interactive snippets, while the messy copyright/IP implications loom large.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast’s Path of Exile Legacy of Phrecia 2.0 start is pure gauntlet chaos—dentist delays, Witch-mule gem shenanigans, brutal modifiers—and the facepalm reveal he ran level 1 gems to level 34&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm kicks off 2026 grumbling about WordPress themes (Nook’s a maybe, Twenty Twelve’s ancient), retires “Search Terms of the Month,” and rolls through last year’s EVE Online and Steam-sale memories&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/383929da8f2365a4558ea7d86b8e98269de05f5ed1d07cadf236868c872b7e7c.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naithin celebrates (a bit late) Time to Loot turning seven, digs into posts/comments/traffic stats, and looks ahead to 2026 hype—especially hoping Crimson Desert delivers after mixed Monster Hunter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold is 85 hours deep in Enshrouded and loves how its voxel building, crafting, housing, and RPG adventuring feels like the MMO dream (UO/SWG-style) that WoW’s quest treadmill never delivered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker shares The Marsh Family’s haunting “Minnesota,” a “San Francisco” adaptation responding to Minneapolis occupation and murders, and argues we need more musicians meeting this moment head&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier’s Friday Squid Blogging spotlights a newly filmed deep-sea squid that buries itself upside-down and pretends to be a plant—equal parts novel, puzzling, and wonderfully weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae tries Nobara (Fedora 43) on a ROG Zephyrus G14 hoping for easy NVIDIA/asusctl wins, but ends up stuck in BIOS weirdness and “why won’t the GPU turn off” driver-manual purgatory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski wants someone else to craft a maximally malicious “zipbomb JSON,” after his ~182‑million nesting-depth attempt hits parser limits—now it’s about balancing depth and array size for RAM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush riffs on the “self-insert Mary Sue” trope, admitting her self-inserts were mostly punching bags—tracking the evolution from a middle-school paracosm to Qibli in TIR, trauma and all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-01.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
