<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 12:02:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-11.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace explains why she bailed on the EverQuest 2 and Wurm Online creator programs: weekly content obligations for a sub fee wasn’t worth it, and she’d rather play and create on her own terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp hits level 30 on a WoW Classic Shaman, celebrates new abilities like Windfury and Astral Recall, and enjoys steady progress thanks to a zone-hopping guide that keeps the journey feeling fresh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa recounts a rough Frosthaven return in “Glowing Catacombs,” tanking as Banner Spear while undead and endlessly-splitting oozes nearly overwhelm the team—until the switches finally flip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss digs into Baldur’s Gate 3 Act III momentum, admits to “cheating” with saves and guides, and shares the satisfying discovery that Orin’s scary “invulnerability” is really just seven attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista checks in on Floatopia, the cosy life sim teased at Gamescom 2024 for 2025, and wonders what’s going on now that it’s February 2026 with near-total radio silence from the team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna reviews Dogpile after 9 hours, calling it a chaotic roguelike deckbuilder where you merge dog cards into bigger dogs, chase bone goals, and stack absurd tags that make the yard go wild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/00a271d2893a22838427a2ae57d461aabec3783c448be225e736a6b9a9d667c3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar reflects on waking early to game out of habit, tracing how World of Warcraft once connected him to his son, and wrestling with sunk cost versus what that daily routine is really trading away now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar tours WoW’s revamped Exile’s Reach, spotting Thrall, Kalecgos, and Wrathion folded into a cleaner Dragon Isles handoff, plus tutorial tweaks like forced gear damage and a new finale rescue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm heads back to Guild Wars Reforged, tweaks the party for more healing, and learns the hard way that Garfazz Bloodfang plus roaming Charr can turn “how hard could it be?” into a wipe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin dives into Zork/Mini-Zork combat code, showing how an off-by-one loop means the cyclops (or thief) never attacks—making the point that “bug” depends on what the designers intended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker argues for reading people you disagree with as “measuring sticks,” embracing the discomfort of challenged convictions as the best way to test, refine, and strengthen your own beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer drops a 15-minute podcast drawing parallels between Frontier-on-Mac and today’s WordLand/WordPress world, plus a note on using Claude.ai for third-person episode summaries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-11.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-10.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar’s MoP Classic honeymoon fades after Golden Lotus and Vale defense, with Skyshard and Wrathion cloak grinds feeling slow—though fishing up the Sea Turtle mount helps a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm looks back at EVE Online’s skill extractors/injectors debut (remember Aurum?) and how “helping new players” quickly turned into a rich-get-richer SP market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold’s 18-hour Menace take: lots of juicy squad-leader builds, gear choices, and faction unlocks, but the game’s depth comes with an accessibility hurdle that makes onboarding rough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f0059d27315e1b199d6d67be9b2f27f0212da08fbb262a6db2ee17875f60450e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;WCRobinson digs into Hyrule Warriors: Age of Imprisonment as a Tears of the Kingdom tie-in, weighing the 1v100 hack-and-slash grind against a bigger spotlight for Zelda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/59c55e8dc574fbf4dd8a65433705a22f80cc3d4166e55270e4d70fed37fd2950.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heartless shrugs at the Super Bowl with a “who cares” drive-by post, basically letting a meme do the talking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast drops a new Mixtape Mondays playlist anchored by Twenty One Pilots’ “Heathens,” with Suicide Squad/Joker vibes and a tracklist built to keep that uncanny mood flowing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7ca8850a216c596b9fa7946ac5d978c12a6d9ab6d182767e9f85f99126d85f44.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole breaks down 1989’s strip mahjong Mahjong Daireikai on Jaleco Mega System 1, showing how hardware choices (tilemaps over sprites) and an undumped security microcontroller shaped the game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier lays out how generative AI floods magazines, journals, courts, lawmakers, and social media with submissions—and why it’s pushing everyone into a messy AI-vs-AI detection arms race.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer flags an https gotcha breaking Drummer/oldschool.scripting.com templates (mixed http assets), then gently nudges loyal readers toward the nightly Scripting News email roundup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/fad5fbde0fef564f781ac5b7a5c1a0d4665780a14f119afa209f1585a9e70264.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete returns from a moving/unpacking hiatus, talks using AI constantly but experimenting less, shares progress on a vibe-coded game-picker app, and says a custom ChatGPT tutor is teaching him TypeS​c​&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger reviews Danny Robins’ Into the Uncanny, praising its even-handed believer/skeptic tone, strong research, and empathetic interviews that make the paranormal cases feel grounded and human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 10 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush kicks off monthly recaps: snowy boredom, dorm cleanup exhaustion, classes canceled, plus goals like Tadlet Kingdom Adventures and rereading Wings of Fire ahead of book 16.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-10.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-09.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar revisits SWTOR’s Knights of the Fallen Empire and, gripes aside, gives it credit—especially for upgraded cutscenes that make your character look consistently screenshot-worthy and badass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi pokes at Zanac’s “AI” ALC difficulty control, then tests runs with no shooting to see how the 1986 Famicom Disk System shmup adapts enemies, bullets, and patterns on the fly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast and crew talk Infinity terrain-building, Rabbit and Steel’s expansion, the games they never got around to (hello, Ys), Ashes of Creation’s implosion, and learning Star Trek Online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm’s Fantasy Critic League hits week six with Dragon Quest VII Reimagined and Nioh 3 finally posting strong review scores, reshuffling the top spots as more updates roll in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/383929da8f2365a4558ea7d86b8e98269de05f5ed1d07cadf236868c872b7e7c.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naithin’s January journal covers a growing Steam backlog, finally hitting Blue Prince’s Antechamber/Room 46 milestone, and a quick note on wrapping up Wuthering Waves 3.1’s main story quest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush finishes Lorelei and the Laser Eyes (nearly 96%!) and loves its randomized puzzle solutions over Blue Prince’s approach, even while dunking on clunky one-hand keyboard controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin digs into Zork I’s combat math—villain tables, nine-sided dice, and knockout nastiness—and adds a new Combat tab to Visible Zork 1 to visualize the whole messy system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7f9c98859b88a8b4676749ce0b1f066770e4ec3e6f2a915e1b885b979b0c6033.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Axxuy celebrates the web’s niche-enthusiasm side by “getting into popcorn,” finding recipes and the r/popcorn community, and ordering genuinely better kernels from Amish Country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily weighs gambling’s addictiveness against “moderation with limits,” vents about Ontario’s nonstop online-casino ads, and points to fake-currency casino apps as a safer dopamine hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a90620097624cae57edb193379e4a70f87b34096acc7c5d0b07d957b947a3e22.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Bray’s “Long Links” round-up bounces from Piketty and misinformation to open-source clothing, weird JWST discoveries, Willie Nelson, listening parties, and the emptying-out of tiny studio flats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer riffs on always-on campaigning in the Twitter era, a Bluesky dialog-box art/joke that actually lands, and a strong recommendation for HBO’s two-part Mel Brooks interview.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 9 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae documents getting non-Steam FFXIV running with ReShade on CachyOS (Wayland/KDE) via xivlauncher tweaks and scripts, with a pragmatic “here’s what worked for me” walkthrough.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-09.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-08.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren tries the free Steam demo for Grandpa’s Bee Haven, a cozy idle beekeeping game inspired by Rusty’s Retirement, praising Mihkel’s responsiveness while noting WIP quirks like monitor-locking and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/fe42e011903d89462478749d0e0bc0c074ddc1fcc05c1a8dac35457669c9e0cb.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cliffski shows off Ridiculous Space Battles’ evolving deployment UI, especially color-coded weapon range/fire-arc overlays and tooltip tweaks that (mostly) keep big multi-ship selections from turning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux says Owlcat’s The Expanse: Osiris Reborn trailer nails the show’s weighty “camera language,” and highlights dev-diary RPG choices like flexible playstyles, eventual commitment, and c&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/13e03e86c44c4a717ee9bf23aad9260659ea0c634b9355db5abb1683bf1ae41f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wes drops a travel-sickened but tasty follow-up: more from his chat with Taki Udon on the SuperStation’s disc-playing dock and real-time CD performance on MiSTer, plus a quick interview with Rain on Q&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael rounds up indie goodness: the “Gaming Like It’s 1930” jam results, Indiepocalypse issue 73, LITHOBREAKERS’ space batch (including a new MUD!), Amiga/Mega65/Game Boy Color Roguecraft DX, and t&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into Apple TV’s The Last Frontier, calling out the goofy Alaska plane-diversion setup while it settles into a mystery-prisoner arc plus “fugitive of the week” survival beats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger chronicles a classic toolchain domino effect: swapping from Corel VideoStudio to Movavi (and fighting freezes from an Action! conflict), then dialing in a Yeti X in Audacity—only to discover the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski quotes Baldur Bjarnason on why arguing with LLM “copilot/agent” true believers is pointless, framing “AI” as unethical, harm-enabling, and fundamentally an attack on labor and education&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer tours his WordPress-powered Scripting News refresh, shares a favorite snarky slogan, grumbles about fake Facebook videos, and nods to the NBA tanking/lottery debate and programming “next-h&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/c5873e60829a051ea50c326795aa4335c0a3d468a1c4bb7e05680a9c703b04e5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa weighs adding every Blaugust signup to the Daily Blogroll, noting RSS/branding gaps and a 12-blog display limit, then nerds out on a rewrite that refactors folders and complicates CSS/templates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin lights up his home office with a programmable LED strip, sharing photos, videos, and the declarative wave-based pattern language he built (after detours through Rust, Raspberry Pi, and&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a77cddcecfc61fbf8bf86d890608ebec7f9e53c1914abd9655fbfee615c2fb59.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 8 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juhis republishes a Q&amp;A with Zachary Kai about hosting the IndieWeb Carnival, explaining why he picked “creative environments,” how he worded an open prompt, and teasing a May 2026 theme on love l&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-08.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-07.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp’s WoW Classic shaman cruises through the 20s with ghost wolf speed, enjoys underrated zones like Stonetalon, and finds a chatty, friendly Christian guild while inching toward level 30.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/195166749a50aa7e93298ae947a7ec0c859d839c7721b3393bcd4fb7a721249e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;John says Perfect Tides: Station to Station is even better-written than the original, and shares a painfully honest uni unrequited-love story to explain how hard this college-relationship game hits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa digs into Funcom’s bumpy Dune: Awakening update (Landsraad specs and a zappy Research Station 152), then chills with Erenshor achievements and eyes Recettear-like Goblin Vyke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux pauses the EVE Online Enforcer grind to try Exploration, gets a Heron from the cosmic signatures chain, and happily faceplants into fittings, probes, cloaks, and “what does this do?” energy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie reviews Super Lesbian Animal RPG, praising its loud-and-proud queer heart and SNES-era JRPG/EarthBound inspirations, plus a note that there’s a podcast version if you’d rather listen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm catches up on Project: Gorgon’s rapid-fire post-1.0 updates and the surprising player-pop bump, while admitting it’s hitting that perfect nostalgia-meets-newness vibe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold reverses course and buys Menace on Steam, arguing the launch discount beats the new PC Game Pass math and lets him dip in and out as patches and content roll in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/3ea0a516c0d87e282ad12bbfc8791eb3c5547d48b6122c839af973d0b3cfd705.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar reflects on leaving measurable corporate validation for the untracked labor of moves, appointments, and home logistics—useful work with no title, no praise, and a harsher feedback loop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier drops his classic Friday Squid Blogging with a Puget Sound squid-fishing tips video, and leaves the comments open for whatever security news folks want to chew on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner watches the OpenClaw/Clawdbot/Moltbot AI-agent hype cycle—powerful, risky, and maybe guardrail-free—plus the weird idea of bots chatting on their own network, Moltbook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer compares Jake’s AI-assisted Frontier kernel spelunking (ChatGPT/Claude) with his own WordLand UI grind, and notes ChatGPT nailed a setTimeout tip like a handy code consultant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 7 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush runs an artist questionnaire, chatting about drawing OCs fast, loving coloring, hating shading, desk-and-plug necessities, and keeping art mostly as a hobby (for now).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-07.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
