<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:57:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-02.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa heads to CaptainCon in Warwick to test her Malifaux crews—swapping between December and Colette du Bois’s Performer misdirection—against a stacked field of top players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux joins Quantshure in EVE Online, traces the “automated” invite back to CCP’s Freelance Jobs funnel, and reflects on how the right corp turns New Eden’s learning cliff into stick-with-it fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna kicks off a newly numbered monthly poll (with a different vibe this time) and shares last month’s results, where “PC + desk” beat out handheld and console couch gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar looks back on WoW’s The War Within ahead of Midnight, admitting it improved a lot and kept her playing, yet still feels “lesser” than the homey high of Dragonflight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast and crew autopsy Anthem’s end, debate what makes an MMO (player interaction required), coin “PSOLikes” for lobby games, then bounce through Shape of Dreams, Path of Exile, and Guild Wars 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm checks in on Fantasy Critic League week five: Highguard limps in at 62, Woolhaven’s score wobbles as reviews roll in, and Code Vein II jitters around the mid-70s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael’s indie roundup tours itch.io oddities and gems—FMV travel, minimalist TTRPG jams, interactive fiction horror, and Early Access FPS MeowGun—plus a nudge to donate to folks in Minnesota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski recaps DNA Pizza’s delivery rollercoaster: from in-house drivers to Uber Eats/Postmates/Grubhub, with app fees gutting margins and the whole delivery-app ecosystem making everything we&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/963329a291b16c942e6e2e48d83f9b7df8d195b72a62616ba711448d655177fe.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friendly Necromancer rounds up recent streaming comfort-food: binging Kevin Smith’s Comic Book Men, getting cozy D&amp;D vibes from Frieren, and tearing through Disney+’s Wonder Man (plus some My Hero&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer riffs on why we needed so many programming languages, imagines modular building blocks for social web apps and bots, and notes nirvana.userland.com is somehow still running since 1998.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/16604299853e3ae7ab27193684e1c47e2a699e21ffea237c029ffd7fc3374aac.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JJM explains ditching cgit for hackable gitweb on git.usebox.net and details the increasingly grim anti-bot toolbox—robots.txt, UA blocks, and a JS cookie redirect—just to keep crawlers out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 2 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger starts a years-long blog “spring clean,” fixing typos and images while tackling embeds and search—and wonders aloud if he should delete off-topic posts to sharpen the site’s focus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-02.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-01.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace captures quiet EVE Online wormhole life: coffee in a freeport, trusty Helios vs tempting Odysseus, and the J-space truth that flying something flashy can be an invitation to die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/b6b344a1f8da7a7f4a6009dad54db841590eed3dca425afcd89d0e8ebec59e67.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nimgimli’s January recap mixes storm prep with SSD-cleanup gaming: lots of My Time at Sandrock and Ball X Pit, bounced off Wasteland 3’s tone, finished Clair Obscur: Expedition 33, and eyes Eternal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss pokes holes in Google’s Project Genie hype: it’s not making real games, just fuzzy 60‑second interactive snippets, while the messy copyright/IP implications loom large.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast’s Path of Exile Legacy of Phrecia 2.0 start is pure gauntlet chaos—dentist delays, Witch-mule gem shenanigans, brutal modifiers—and the facepalm reveal he ran level 1 gems to level 34&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm kicks off 2026 grumbling about WordPress themes (Nook’s a maybe, Twenty Twelve’s ancient), retires “Search Terms of the Month,” and rolls through last year’s EVE Online and Steam-sale memories&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/383929da8f2365a4558ea7d86b8e98269de05f5ed1d07cadf236868c872b7e7c.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naithin celebrates (a bit late) Time to Loot turning seven, digs into posts/comments/traffic stats, and looks ahead to 2026 hype—especially hoping Crimson Desert delivers after mixed Monster Hunter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold is 85 hours deep in Enshrouded and loves how its voxel building, crafting, housing, and RPG adventuring feels like the MMO dream (UO/SWG-style) that WoW’s quest treadmill never delivered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker shares The Marsh Family’s haunting “Minnesota,” a “San Francisco” adaptation responding to Minneapolis occupation and murders, and argues we need more musicians meeting this moment head&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier’s Friday Squid Blogging spotlights a newly filmed deep-sea squid that buries itself upside-down and pretends to be a plant—equal parts novel, puzzling, and wonderfully weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae tries Nobara (Fedora 43) on a ROG Zephyrus G14 hoping for easy NVIDIA/asusctl wins, but ends up stuck in BIOS weirdness and “why won’t the GPU turn off” driver-manual purgatory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski wants someone else to craft a maximally malicious “zipbomb JSON,” after his ~182‑million nesting-depth attempt hits parser limits—now it’s about balancing depth and array size for RAM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0fd763e76df37b9a2050e87691980c6eb52cd95b497e31de1f3448164b0944a4.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 1 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tofutush riffs on the “self-insert Mary Sue” trope, admitting her self-inserts were mostly punching bags—tracking the evolution from a middle-school paracosm to Qibli in TIR, trauma and all.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-01.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-31.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren returns to Project: Gorgon for the 1.0 launch, updates an old character with the improved models and slider-heavy creator, and revisits the busy newbie island and quirky story beats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp recaps a suddenly-busy January and sets February MMO targets: keep leveling in WoW Classic ahead of Burning Crusade Anniversary, chase retail endeavors, finish another LOTRO Harad zone, and dabble&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa goes deep on Othello World for Super Famicom, then iterates from MCTS and negamax to a genetic algorithm to finally build an AI that can beat Long John Silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/66e2840897ab0717fc91b52ca8dbd932b21cf78aa788d0e8d4a2621506fd79cc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frostilyte reviews Super Chipflake Ü, a Banjo-Kazooie-style 3D platformer with great late-’90s vibes and music transitions, but says the fetch-quest slog and limited movement kill the fun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/81e604717a2ab6c86623f9e9ac74e3656194a4b5d9566922afb12ecd3b9efeb0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magi can’t stop playing the Goblin Vyke demo, praising its stealth-first “dungeon steal by night, sell by day” loop, grim greed story setup, and tense trap-and-timing metroidvania dungeon design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d3120fe0d6b9f06f5461243c57b21dc5aff0bffca8fb83a608f18fbe3f861675.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scopique logs Star Citizen’s patch 4.6 “Clear the Air” grind, hauling cargo across Stanton in a Hermes, tracking point payouts, and eyeing huge SCU missions that scream “bring a Hercules.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm rounds up 2026 MMO roadmaps, digging into World of Warcraft retail’s WoW Midnight plans and the split vibes around WoW Classic’s Burning Crusade return and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/963329a291b16c942e6e2e48d83f9b7df8d195b72a62616ba711448d655177fe.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friendly Necromancer checks in with Diablo IV’s new Paladin season antics, celebrates Project Gorgon finally launching out of beta, and shares a hopeful real-life health update.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold plays two Essen pickups: Abroad feels lighter and swingier than its BGG weight suggests, while Fromage surprises with parallel simultaneous turns that keep a medium game snappy and deep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski is delighted (and a little incredulous) that a 15-minute documentary exists about Whale, reminiscing about their Pixies-ish sleaze, Tricky connections, and a pair of very uneven 1998&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker writes from a “dark place,” raging at corruption, arrests, and the Epstein files release—refusing to repeat the worst details, but demanding moral clarity and real accountability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 31 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer ties FOSDEM to his “start over” social web pitch—simple peer-to-peer first, careful centralization tradeoffs—then tweaks wpIdentity storage docs and notes app/object identification is next.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-31.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-30.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren digs into Sundial Games’ solo D20 quest calendar The Souls of Saraku, enjoying the villain-side twist, Notoriety/minion vibes, and—importantly—taking a break from daily live-blogging burnout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar says goodbye to SWTOR creator FibroJedi’s soon-to-vanish site, credits his disability-informed perspective on story modes, and helps preserve old SWTOR posts by tracking them down on the Wayb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/907d0e06534fcd206c847a182352b79b51b35cc38d28937dfc80ec43bacf6a38.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Azuriel is wowed by Clair Obscur: Expedition 33’s trippy art and mocap-driven dialogue, but finds the turn-based Soulslike combat (QTEs, parries, limited healing) a real drag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi loves Alien Breed ’92 Special Edition as a ground-up rebuild with Gauntlet-ish roots turned into tense survival—limited ammo, persistent resources, and nasty door/key choices that haunt yourrun&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie reviews Wavetale as a breezy modern 3D platformer throwback—Sigrid vs The Gloom across ocean islets—scratching that Spyro/Jak-era itch while leaning into a narrative adventure vibe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm looks back on Project: Gorgon’s long road—failed Kickstarters, Steam Early Access, and Sandra Powers’ passing—before finally celebrating its hard-won 1.0 release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger says Der Tiger AKA The Tank isn’t Fury-style WWII action so much as horror-adjacent dread, praising the eerie atmosphere, convincing Tiger tank effects, and strong performances from the crew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael flags reports of ICE detaining parents of Ypsilanti students, urges locals to stay alert and get involved, and pushes back on claims about enforcement pulling out elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski sees Mozilla’s “billion with a B” AI push as an event-horizon moment—if you hoped surveys or feedback would steer the ship, he’s saying it’s already cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer wrangles pagepark.scripting.com hosting weirdness, then riffs on the OG Web as “small pieces loosely joined,” plus some pragmatic notes on goals, code placement, and daily productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/c5873e60829a051ea50c326795aa4335c0a3d468a1c4bb7e05680a9c703b04e5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa “vibe codes” a FastAPI proof-of-concept with Claude Sonnet—REST endpoints, database abstraction, tests, docs, plus Geocod.io and National Weather Service APIs—and admits it worked surprisingly 잘.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner reflects on running theatres: picking a season is basically selling a promise a year ahead, and delivering on it—snowstorms, flops, and all—is what builds the trust that keeps subscribers back.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-30.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-29.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren walks through FFXIV patch 7.41’s Obscurum Phantom relic step, covering the crafted/purchased mats and the Crystal Paste “light” grind via the Phantom Glass activities list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux breaks down why EVE Online’s player-run production, logistics, and trade feel like a real economy—especially since destruction isn’t failure, it’s the demand that keeps everything moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/66e2840897ab0717fc91b52ca8dbd932b21cf78aa788d0e8d4a2621506fd79cc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frostilyte reviews Confidential Killings as a solid point-and-click mystery with Golden Idol-style fill-in puzzles, but says the deduction feels too lightweight to really stand out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar shares her Star Wars: The Old Republic Total Galactic War Conquest routine, breaking objectives into tiers and explaining how she reliably churns out millions of points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna curates a seasonal indie-game list (12 total), leaning into cozy winter vibes like Winter Burrow and ILA: A Frosty Glide, with quick notes on mood and even motion-sickness caveats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/e853d6a4ed4654210b61c733cf9990dc7182a8fb9040b7b14f2222c9a2ba934f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infinitron rounds up news on Ashbane, a turn-based tactical RPG about building a mercenary guild with long-term class progression, risky contracts with consequences, and regular Steam dev updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into Blue Prince, a roguelike-ish puzzle deckbuilder where you draft rooms to reassemble a shifting mansion day by day, homonym jokes firmly left on the table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin corrects his Infocom release timeline—Deadline comes before Zork 3 and Starcross—citing Softalk, the Fact Sheet, and serial numbers while keeping his Patreon plan mostly intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker spotlights Bruce Springsteen’s “Streets of Minneapolis,” loving the no-metaphors, straight-to-the-heart approach and hoping to hear it live at the Grammys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily retells a nightmare that played like sci-fi survival horror: her Star Wars OC gliding through lakes and ruins while an invincible, force-fielded General Grievous relentlessly hunts her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae swaps Nova and a flaky Lawnchair setup for Octopi Launcher on a Pixel 8a, praising stability, deep long-press customization, and the surprisingly handy multiple docks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer warns that Bluesky-only formats are just silos, riffs on AI making StackExchange feel obsolete while knowledge gets locked up, and caps it with a domain-name cautionary tale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-29.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
