<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 11:52:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-25.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren reviews Don’t Touch the Snail, an idle desktop overlay where permadeath is truly permanent—let the snail touch your cursor and you’re locked out forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa says Star Trek Voyager: Across the Unknown finally feels like real Trek, remixing show plot beats with choice-driven crew “heroes” and base-repair management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/81e604717a2ab6c86623f9e9ac74e3656194a4b5d9566922afb12ecd3b9efeb0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magi reviews Grimshire’s cozy-looking farming sim veneer over plague survival, where crop choices, animal traits, and limited skill picks are all about feeding the village.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi explores Everblue 2’s sunny dolphin-photo charm contrasted with claustrophobic wreck dives, currents and light, and a constant “respect the ocean or die” vibe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar weighs the pros and cons of Warlords of Draenor Classic—easy for Blizzard, still-populated Classic realms, but a reputation problem for WoD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast falls back into World of Warcraft via the Valentine’s event and housing curiosity, then dives into transmog raid runs and Auction House selling with TSM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm chases No Man’s Sky Remnant goals, grinding scrap disposal and dozer-smashing until the Colossus exocraft’s furnace chassis finally unlocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin digs into “Learning ZIL” and shows those snarky “Stu should write this” notes make sense in the May 1989 Infocom shutdown context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/fe42e011903d89462478749d0e0bc0c074ddc1fcc05c1a8dac35457669c9e0cb.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cliffski shares fast progress pics on the solar-powered borehole project in Cameroon—dry season urgency, drilling rig on-site, and the water-tower framework already going up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker notes the U.S. president gave a speech, but they chose to spend the night watching Shakespeare instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski reframes AI hype by swapping in “cocaine,” using the productivity-and-value argument to highlight how weird the booster logic sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 25 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer argues AI “agents” are basically server software, and wishes for a Really Simple Language so you can write servers in plain English.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-25.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-24.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace’s WoW goldmaking week: ~3M gold, pets slumping while transmog and recipes sell, and a steady “older items” strategy heading toward Midnight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp decorates a WoW bookshop café, runs delves on a warlock for gear and housing XP, and readies for Midnight while his wife returns post-Dragonflight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux launches “New Eden Banter” with a March 2 prompt: why EVE Online is still thriving after two decades, and how to join the roundup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/66e2840897ab0717fc91b52ca8dbd932b21cf78aa788d0e8d4a2621506fd79cc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frostilyte argues Blighttown (Dark Souls) rules actually, then connects that love of cliffside vertical architecture to mountain-settlement building in Whiskerwood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista rounds up cozy-leaning Steam Next Fest demos to wishlist, from seafaring farming in Collectors Cove to Duck Side of the Moon and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna spotlights Everholm’s 2.0 update (out Feb 19), what she hopes it fixes—especially NPC depth—and includes a short Q&amp;A with Mike from Chonky Loaf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c61bfc5074257f94d1bffdb371ca16e89e7f1ebeb9066604fadd4895167e6a6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew defends his love for Nintendo’s Virtual Boy, gets hyped for Switch Online’s Virtual Boy library, and grudgingly buys the pricey replica headset.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d3120fe0d6b9f06f5461243c57b21dc5aff0bffca8fb83a608f18fbe3f861675.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scopique tries SpaceCraft’s Steam Next Fest demo: start in debt, mine planets, refine and craft ship parts, and tinker with modular components over a long tutorial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger lays out why paranormal research is a mess—sensationalism, religion, conspiracies, and charlatans—then argues even “ghosts” needs a usable definition first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier flags research showing server-side control can undermine cloud password managers (especially recovery/sharing), and pitches Password Safe for no-cloud, no-recovery encryption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer chronicles an easier-than-hyped snow day, plugs a web/evolution essay and an AI-for-customer-service podcast, and yes, really simple ravioli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 24 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm dunks on Zuckerberg’s metaverse obsession as Meta Horizon Worlds heads to mobile, framing it as a costly, luck-driven “second act” chase.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-24.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-23.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa heads back to Malifaux to tempt new players at a store event, then faces old nemesis Dave—Colette du Bois (Colette 2, soulstone shenanigans) versus Maxine Agassiz, with hobby updates on Frosthave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar reposts (with permission) and updates FJ Brodie’s SWTOR guide to Makeb’s relaxing GSI daily/weekly missions—maps, where to dig with the Seeker Droid, and what you’ll earn at the current level&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7ca8850a216c596b9fa7946ac5d978c12a6d9ab6d182767e9f85f99126d85f44.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole gushes over retro hardware tinkerers after ordering enthusiast-made Sega-ish consoles via AliExpress, spotlighting an orange “MD3” Genesis 3-style unit with a gorgeous PCB—and a Saturn-style AV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/13e03e86c44c4a717ee9bf23aad9260659ea0c634b9355db5abb1683bf1ae41f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wes rounds up emulation/preservation news: Dolphin’s Triforce arcade progress (with one stubborn holdout), a native PC port for Rockman EXE: Phantom of Network, Secret of Mana: Reborn updates, and an&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast and the AggroChat crew dig into what’s changed in Dune Awakening, then bounce through Enshrouded’s Hollow Halls, Shape of Dreams runs, Towerbolt, Star Trek Online buildcraft, and hype for La&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie’s Castlevania Chronicles review celebrates this PS1 port of the X68000 remake as a “fantastic game,” and reflects on just how many Castlevania remixes and reimaginings Konami kept spinning off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm’s Fantasy Critic League update is mostly calm—High on Life 2 dips a bit, rankings shuffle, a Castlevania: Belmont’s Curse bid lands, and counter-picks hit Always In Mind and Diablo IV: Lord of&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae’s week 8 digest mixes insomnia and housing/job stress with reading notes on Gladys Mitchell’s Mrs Bradley mysteries (Dead Men’s Morris, Come Away, Death), plus Olympics, Raidou, Fate/GO Val&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily reflects on what patriotism means to her as a Canadian, describing recent spikes amid Trump’s tariff/annexation threats, buying Canadian brands, traveling domestically (East coast plans), and y&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael’s smaller weekly roundup links indie game roundups (Jank, Mothership), notes Discord’s bad calls pushing him back to forums, and tosses in music, poetry issues, and even raspberry cheesecake b&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer argues the web “builds on the web”: podcasting leaned on MP3, tech evolution can’t rewind, and “don’t invent” beats VC dreams—plus he points at AI’s killer app: customer service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a7160b714eadfbf19b80d74adfae89df8119259876f1b1af521595d09edcc1f1.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 23 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oya vents (dramatically, by design) about live-action adaptations of animated works, sparked by Netflix’s Avatar: The Last Airbender Season 2 promo, while stressing her criticisms aren’t aimed at the&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-23.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-22.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp plays WoW Classic Anniversary at his own pace—still level 34 while everyone hits Outland—embracing a chill Shaman journey, lively Stormwind, and a love/hate trudge through Stranglethorn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa digs into why miniatures gaming (Frosthaven, Malifaux, even WH40K vibes) feels so niche: social anxiety, opacity, and that hefty up-front minis investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/907d0e06534fcd206c847a182352b79b51b35cc38d28937dfc80ec43bacf6a38.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Azuriel is 30 hours deep into Mewgenics, praising its crude McMillen charm and busted combos while warning the tactical roguelite cat-breeding loop is brutal, punishes mistakes, and even hates save-sc&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/81e604717a2ab6c86623f9e9ac74e3656194a4b5d9566922afb12ecd3b9efeb0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magi reviews Cash Cleaner Simulator, a cozy-satirical job sim where you’re kidnapped into literally laundering cash—sorting denominations, spotting counterfeits, cleaning gunk, and upgrading gear as a&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi revisits Super Mario Land on Game Boy and argues its oddball vibes are intentional—superballs, weird enemies and worlds, surprisingly lush details, and a challenge ramp that gets real fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm breaks down EVE Online’s WinterCo pausing its offensive versus INIT, shifting to defense as Goons poke Geminate, and calls out the bloc-math spin with DOTLAN numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael celebrates Gobliiins 6 by tracing the weird French point-and-click series back to 1991, its switch-between-goblins puzzle format, and the Pierre Gilhodes/Muriel Tramis legacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski highlights an SF jury pool getting slashed as potential jurors aired intense anti–Elon Musk feelings, including “existence of billionaires” objections and Twitter-moderation beef.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner reminisces about learning slide rules and old-school drafting for theatre design, appreciates software’s speed, and wonders how the next wave of AI might replace even more hands-on fundamentals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a90620097624cae57edb193379e4a70f87b34096acc7c5d0b07d957b947a3e22.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Bray wrestles with using GenAI on his open-source Quamina project—after some happy Claude-assisted PRs—while still arguing the broader LLM industry’s incentives are grim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer drops a new podcast about losing his Twitter account, then riffs on vibe coding codebase rewrites, how to run polls without Twitter, and being deeply over the snow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 22 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar reflects on blogging about World of Warcraft from Wrath to WoW Classic, missing the old link-and-response community, and digging into Google indexing and which posts still pull clicks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-22.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-21.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/66e2840897ab0717fc91b52ca8dbd932b21cf78aa788d0e8d4a2621506fd79cc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frostilyte, fresh off a rough illness streak, digs into the Reptilian Rising demo: vaporwave tactics with action-figure heroes vs talking dinosaurs, where turn timers push you to play aggressive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/01e4904d0e7166d1e9ffa1978135f08734bbf9ead03a4e6627b83c2add7501cd.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sey rounds up indie goodness: wishlist-worthy Demon Tides, a wildly overfunded Gun Nose Kickstarter, a surprise Neva DLC + Berlinist soundtrack, and Super Rare Games’ big art book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d3120fe0d6b9f06f5461243c57b21dc5aff0bffca8fb83a608f18fbe3f861675.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scopique cheers Star Trek Voyager – Across the Unknown for actually ‘getting’ Trek, blending show-driven narrative with tense resource-scanning, turn-by-turn travel where deuterium and food tick down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast says farewell to his Path of Exile Phrecia 2.0 Arakaali minion build, speculates on the next league’s opaque teasers, and keeps tinkering in Dune Awakening toward buggies and cobalt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm wraps No Man’s Sky Expedition 21 (Remnant) with hard-earned Colossus trucking lessons—pack smart, avoid slopes, and pray the cargo doesn’t yeet itself into a ravine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/963329a291b16c942e6e2e48d83f9b7df8d195b72a62616ba711448d655177fe.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friendly Necromancer finally tries Mewgenics and comes away sold on its turn-based roguelike cat-breeding chaos, smart synergies, and ‘how is this so good?’ polish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold argues Civilization VII’s unpopular three-era reset is getting quietly reversed in Spring 2026’s ‘Test of Time’ update—basically turning Civ 7 into a more Civ 6-like “7.5.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss vents about streaming rights roulette (hello, Lucifer and Roswell New Mexico) and wonders if buying DVDs again makes more sense—especially with Gen Z fuelling a physical-media comeback.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily answers the big question—favorite candy—by staking out Team Chocolate, with Lindt Lindor, Nestle Crunch, and Cadbury Mini Eggs leading the pack (plus occasional dark chocolate compromises).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ac498263c07a3920e96459f262f0ccd30c02447d27bdae5229beff3f7568c007.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blockade85 feels winter finally cracking—longer days, Spring Training hope, and that annual pull back toward big Final Fantasy XI goals after surviving an Ohio freeze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier drops a Friday Squid Blogging cartoon link and opens the floor for whatever security stories the community wants to hash out in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 21 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer points to an updated FeedLand Docker Compose for running locally, crowdsources OPML/feed-product news lists, and shares how he trained ChatGPT/Claude to indent code for his outliner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-21.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
