<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 11:57:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-15.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss reacts to Playable Worlds layoffs on Stars Reach, pointing out it’s still pre-alpha and that trimming the only-game studio this early feels like a serious warning sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7ca8850a216c596b9fa7946ac5d978c12a6d9ab6d182767e9f85f99126d85f44.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole rants about misinformation after trying to look up Phantasy Star Fukkokuban (a Master System game packaged in a Genesis cart), and getting sketchy-seeming search results alongside stalwarts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar skips the Account Played addon but still totals her WoW /played time, sharing a top-five list where her original 2007 character dwarfs the rest and a MoP Classic hunter surprisingly hits #2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast tries Diablo II’s surprise Warlock class (shadow-dropped and feeling hilariously overpowered), notes it’s coming to Diablo IV and Diablo Immortal too, and checks out Destiny Rising’s LunarNew&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into Playable World’s “reorganization” (read: layoffs) on Stars Reach, noting the classic Friday-after-4pm timing and the uneasy déjà vu of MMO staffing cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin didn’t hit the $500/month Patreon goal, but he’s building Zork 3 anyway—bare-bones build already running, with plans to finish Zork 3, Deadline, and Starcross by May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger spotlights London’s British Optical Association Museum—a charming Georgian-house “hidden gem” with a witty curator-led optometry history tour, from old signage to a Harry Potter glasses display.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski riffs on the SF blackout hearing: PG&amp;E says the mayor requested power for the War Memorial Opera House, then later calls it a “misunderstanding,” and JWZ wonders why PG&amp;E would do him&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner rounds up a Sunday reading list about staying aware amid “something big” (AI), plus essays on art, social “rewilding,” screenless tech skepticism, nuance, surveillance, winter firewood demand,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae lists their daily-driver setup after moving from Windows 11 to CachyOS (KDE Plasma 6/Wayland), sticking with Firefox for everyday browsing and using Brave for DRM-heavy streaming sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier posts his upcoming speaking calendar—Ontario Tech, Personal AI Summit, WSJ Tech Live: Cybersecurity, the Ross Anderson Lecture at Cambridge, and RSAC 2026—so you can catch him live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Sunday, 15 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer vents about browsers hiding RSS feeds, “tiny-little-text-box” social apps that break the Back button, and even suggests AIs should take a run at Wikipedia’s errors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-15.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-14.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp remodels his World of Warcraft house room-by-room, juggles prepatch world-boss grind and transmog tinkering, and recruits his daughter to help build a cozy ’90s coffeehouse/bookstore alt-café.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa checks out Othello Trigger, a Chrono Trigger riff that’s mostly Othello, and nerds out over cramming characters, screens, and discs into tiny Game Boy Color memory via GB Studio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi dives into the 2000 PC Legend of the Sacred Stone tie-in, praising its action-RPG simplicity, mouse-driven combat rhythm, and gnarly payoffs like decapitations and fiery magic explosions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f8abd39a6afc005f4c16e963f7d05f2f0fa7d744c8e578cfe3c17ede0d594faa.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mailvaltar can’t believe Diablo II: Resurrected actually got an expansion—new class, items/runewords, endgame, loot filter, and currency stash tabs—then curses being too sick to play yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm runs Friday-the-13th bullet points on gamers hating gen-AI “slop” (survey stats and all) and Discord’s looming age verification pitch—government IDs, backlash, and “we’ll use AI” reassurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael’s indie roundup plugs the No ICE in Minnesota Itch bundle, gushes over Africanfuturist heist game Relooted, celebrates doodle-racer Gradient.horse, and notes new/renewed adventure games and B&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss dusts off the listening diary with 13 Friday-the-13th picks, shouting out videos like A$AP Rocky’s “Punk Rocky” and digging into synth/glam-punk-ish vibes with plenty of side commentary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski drops a Valentine’s-adjacent “previously” link chain—a greatest-hits trail of past oddities and Xscreensaver-adjacent posts to click around and lose an afternoon to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae shares a no-frills desk setup and a rant about “best of” gamer gear elitism, spotlighting practical picks like an 8BitDo Lite 2 controller and a thrifted 27" 1080p monitor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker tears into a NYT-reported Meta memo about facial recognition in smart glasses, warning about privacy harms, “dynamic political environment” timing, and creepy real-world misuse already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer argues news should become a distributed, unownable, replaceable system (with AI QA overseen by a nonprofit of retired journalists), then raves about Anker open-ear earbuds being weirdly, aw&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/16604299853e3ae7ab27193684e1c47e2a699e21ffea237c029ffd7fc3374aac.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Saturday, 14 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JJM wires up a day-friendly light theme toggle across Neovim, tmux, and wezterm via a custom :ToggleLights command, some Lua, and a marker-file hack because wezterm won’t cooperate remotely.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-14.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-13.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren reviews Flufftopia: Fluffmazing Edition—cute piggy-bank clicker town-building that runs fine on Steam Deck (tiny UI caveats), then quietly hints at a clever, darker twist and multiple endings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp talks about hitting an “ebb” in LOTRO—logging in more from duty than excitement—so he’s keeping play light until the spark returns, while enjoying touches like adorable elephants and the Grey&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux gets parachuted into a Fallout TTRPG set in a brutal Boston winter and rolls up a Mister Handy with a sketchy “security update,” joining a Vault pedicurist, scavenger, and lucid ghoul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista celebrates Starsand Island hitting Steam Early Access/Xbox Preview, pitching its cozy life-sim mix of farming, fishing, animal care, exploration, romance, and island mysteries—with community-sh&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/51c04925b679dacd0ef9aa40f9c4598d64613840613c00e2dc4c20ddf92463b7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pixel One vents about a live-service edge case: a paid character transfer token fails, support follows the script, then closes the ticket as “resolved” anyway—KPI theater over fixing the block.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/e853d6a4ed4654210b61c733cf9990dc7182a8fb9040b7b14f2222c9a2ba934f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;RPG Codex flags that Sector Unknown is out, slotting it into their rapid-fire headline stream of RPG releases and announcements for anyone tracking what’s newly shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into No Man’s Sky Update 6.2 “Remnant,” where the Colossus exocraft gets serious customization plus scrap-world industrial waste collecting and Waste Processing Plants to toot at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5eab042fa5f26dc78cd61970dacb37f229e43eb745dc89b71838f854799eddcc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghastly’s fed up with GOG’s generative-AI promo stance and points to DRM-free alternatives like zoom-platform and Fire Flower Games, plus preservation-minded exoDOS for old DOS titles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger lays out a UK household’s monthly budget reality—council tax, utilities, travel, groceries, housing—and why inflation and annual April price hikes make cutting costs feel like a grim puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski marvels that you can effectively DoS a Waymo by leaving its door open, and dunks on the fix: paying DoorDash drivers about $10 to go close it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/68c66ed0ede8d574d6a8213a6cbcef70bb70ab39905e045b8876758031895fec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bruce Schneier breaks down a New York proposal to add “blocking technology” to 3D printers that scans every file for firearm blueprints, arguing it’s DRM-style policy that won’t work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 13 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer asks Docker-capable folks to test FeedLand’s new easier setup and help bootstrap the “feediverse,” then riffs on AI intelligence debates and a ChatGPT “it listens” anecdote.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-13.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-12.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren checks in with Steam Deck-friendly backlog nibbling—Toy Tinker Simulator’s charm despite jank, Castle Flipper’s cheap-but-mixed vibes, and a promising Arcanium roguelite card-battler party hook&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/59c55e8dc574fbf4dd8a65433705a22f80cc3d4166e55270e4d70fed37fd2950.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heartless argues ARC Raiders’ stash-value “departure” meta pushes players to sell the fun stuff; make trinkets worth more and guns/materials worth less so people actually bring gear topside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/81e604717a2ab6c86623f9e9ac74e3656194a4b5d9566922afb12ecd3b9efeb0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magi spotlights “Shinies for Good,” a week-long Twitch Pokémon shiny-hunting fundraiser (Feb 10–16) backing the American Immigration Council, with donations supporting litigation, research, and pro-b&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/e853d6a4ed4654210b61c733cf9990dc7182a8fb9040b7b14f2222c9a2ba934f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;RPG Codex notes THQ Nordic and Alkimia Interactive set Gothic 1 Remake for June 5, 2026 on PC/PS5/Xbox, aiming to modernize without losing the original’s gritty “Colony” vibe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast is still deep in Path of Exile’s Legacy of Phrecia, hyped for a tanky, high-damage minion build (Spectres/Animate Guardian) while pushing Delve and eyeing voidstones before 3.28 lands&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm meant to just peek at Project: Gorgon, then lost a weekend to it—tweaked graphics from “poor” to “good,” and vibed hard with its do-stuff-to-level-skills progression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss chews on Discord’s age verification backlash—if everyone’s been breached anyway, is this about security, principle, or old-internet nostalgia, especially when we also demand platforms protect&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/3ea0a516c0d87e282ad12bbfc8791eb3c5547d48b6122c839af973d0b3cfd705.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar’s advice for new accountants: master the basics, but prioritize judgment, read incentives, protect integrity strategically, and build transferable skills like clear writing and communication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael shares a grab-bag of links—music, TTRPG map-writing prompts, self-hosting a music library, and a bunch of new indie/video game sites worth tossing in your RSS reader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner revisits iOS 26 Phone app changes, finding Hold Assist and call screening awkward in real life (even for medical offices), and still wants spam reporting and delete options made way more direct&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d3120fe0d6b9f06f5461243c57b21dc5aff0bffca8fb83a608f18fbe3f861675.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scopique’s cooler-headed Discord take: “teen by default” age verification (ID or selfie) going global, plus worries about AI parsing, data retention, and trust after a prior breach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 12 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer flags a Docker setup for FeedLand, wants news.scripting.com faster and easier to clone, muses on Life on Our Planet, and goes digging for early blogger takes on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-12.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-11.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace explains why she bailed on the EverQuest 2 and Wurm Online creator programs: weekly content obligations for a sub fee wasn’t worth it, and she’d rather play and create on her own terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp hits level 30 on a WoW Classic Shaman, celebrates new abilities like Windfury and Astral Recall, and enjoys steady progress thanks to a zone-hopping guide that keeps the journey feeling fresh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa recounts a rough Frosthaven return in “Glowing Catacombs,” tanking as Banner Spear while undead and endlessly-splitting oozes nearly overwhelm the team—until the switches finally flip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/370859dab59b0eaef5dd8adc2ae7a3e17546088d56096ab5393084886c36110e.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhagpuss digs into Baldur’s Gate 3 Act III momentum, admits to “cheating” with saves and guides, and shares the satisfying discovery that Orin’s scary “invulnerability” is really just seven attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista checks in on Floatopia, the cosy life sim teased at Gamescom 2024 for 2025, and wonders what’s going on now that it’s February 2026 with near-total radio silence from the team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna reviews Dogpile after 9 hours, calling it a chaotic roguelike deckbuilder where you merge dog cards into bigger dogs, chase bone goals, and stack absurd tags that make the yard go wild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/00a271d2893a22838427a2ae57d461aabec3783c448be225e736a6b9a9d667c3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar reflects on waking early to game out of habit, tracing how World of Warcraft once connected him to his son, and wrestling with sunk cost versus what that daily routine is really trading away now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar tours WoW’s revamped Exile’s Reach, spotting Thrall, Kalecgos, and Wrathion folded into a cleaner Dragon Isles handoff, plus tutorial tweaks like forced gear damage and a new finale rescue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm heads back to Guild Wars Reforged, tweaks the party for more healing, and learns the hard way that Garfazz Bloodfang plus roaming Charr can turn “how hard could it be?” into a wipe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin dives into Zork/Mini-Zork combat code, showing how an off-by-one loop means the cyclops (or thief) never attacks—making the point that “bug” depends on what the designers intended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker argues for reading people you disagree with as “measuring sticks,” embracing the discomfort of challenged convictions as the best way to test, refine, and strengthen your own beliefs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 11 February 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer drops a 15-minute podcast drawing parallels between Frontier-on-Mac and today’s WordLand/WordPress world, plus a note on using Claude.ai for third-person episode summaries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/02/daily-blogroll-2026-02-11.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
