<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Daily Blogroll</title>
    <link>http://westkarana.xyz</link>
    <description>Daily Blogroll, now in XML!</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 10:26:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-30.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren digs into Sundial Games’ solo D20 quest calendar The Souls of Saraku, enjoying the villain-side twist, Notoriety/minion vibes, and—importantly—taking a break from daily live-blogging burnout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar says goodbye to SWTOR creator FibroJedi’s soon-to-vanish site, credits his disability-informed perspective on story modes, and helps preserve old SWTOR posts by tracking them down on the Wayb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/907d0e06534fcd206c847a182352b79b51b35cc38d28937dfc80ec43bacf6a38.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Azuriel is wowed by Clair Obscur: Expedition 33’s trippy art and mocap-driven dialogue, but finds the turn-based Soulslike combat (QTEs, parries, limited healing) a real drag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi loves Alien Breed ’92 Special Edition as a ground-up rebuild with Gauntlet-ish roots turned into tense survival—limited ammo, persistent resources, and nasty door/key choices that haunt yourrun&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie reviews Wavetale as a breezy modern 3D platformer throwback—Sigrid vs The Gloom across ocean islets—scratching that Spyro/Jak-era itch while leaning into a narrative adventure vibe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm looks back on Project: Gorgon’s long road—failed Kickstarters, Steam Early Access, and Sandra Powers’ passing—before finally celebrating its hard-won 1.0 release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger says Der Tiger AKA The Tank isn’t Fury-style WWII action so much as horror-adjacent dread, praising the eerie atmosphere, convincing Tiger tank effects, and strong performances from the crew.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael flags reports of ICE detaining parents of Ypsilanti students, urges locals to stay alert and get involved, and pushes back on claims about enforcement pulling out elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski sees Mozilla’s “billion with a B” AI push as an event-horizon moment—if you hoped surveys or feedback would steer the ship, he’s saying it’s already cooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer wrangles pagepark.scripting.com hosting weirdness, then riffs on the OG Web as “small pieces loosely joined,” plus some pragmatic notes on goals, code placement, and daily productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/c5873e60829a051ea50c326795aa4335c0a3d468a1c4bb7e05680a9c703b04e5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa “vibe codes” a FastAPI proof-of-concept with Claude Sonnet—REST endpoints, database abstraction, tests, docs, plus Geocod.io and National Weather Service APIs—and admits it worked surprisingly 잘.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Friday, 30 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner reflects on running theatres: picking a season is basically selling a promise a year ahead, and delivering on it—snowstorms, flops, and all—is what builds the trust that keeps subscribers back.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-30.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-29.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren walks through FFXIV patch 7.41’s Obscurum Phantom relic step, covering the crafted/purchased mats and the Crystal Paste “light” grind via the Phantom Glass activities list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux breaks down why EVE Online’s player-run production, logistics, and trade feel like a real economy—especially since destruction isn’t failure, it’s the demand that keeps everything moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/66e2840897ab0717fc91b52ca8dbd932b21cf78aa788d0e8d4a2621506fd79cc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frostilyte reviews Confidential Killings as a solid point-and-click mystery with Golden Idol-style fill-in puzzles, but says the deduction feels too lightweight to really stand out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar shares her Star Wars: The Old Republic Total Galactic War Conquest routine, breaking objectives into tiers and explaining how she reliably churns out millions of points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d5aa35cf405ada4830b06e48a455bc3dface18780837979cae727683cd332cd7.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luna curates a seasonal indie-game list (12 total), leaning into cozy winter vibes like Winter Burrow and ILA: A Frosty Glide, with quick notes on mood and even motion-sickness caveats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/e853d6a4ed4654210b61c733cf9990dc7182a8fb9040b7b14f2222c9a2ba934f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infinitron rounds up news on Ashbane, a turn-based tactical RPG about building a mercenary guild with long-term class progression, risky contracts with consequences, and regular Steam dev updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm digs into Blue Prince, a roguelike-ish puzzle deckbuilder where you draft rooms to reassemble a shifting mansion day by day, homonym jokes firmly left on the table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c88590fbb18bf43c3ef939ebf390c35e3eff0d60962f8809ee6539997e5b7b8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew Plotkin corrects his Infocom release timeline—Deadline comes before Zork 3 and Starcross—citing Softalk, the Fact Sheet, and serial numbers while keeping his Patreon plan mostly intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner Crocker spotlights Bruce Springsteen’s “Streets of Minneapolis,” loving the no-metaphors, straight-to-the-heart approach and hoping to hear it live at the Grammys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily retells a nightmare that played like sci-fi survival horror: her Star Wars OC gliding through lakes and ruins while an invincible, force-fielded General Grievous relentlessly hunts her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae swaps Nova and a flaky Lawnchair setup for Octopi Launcher on a Pixel 8a, praising stability, deep long-press customization, and the surprisingly handy multiple docks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Thursday, 29 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer warns that Bluesky-only formats are just silos, riffs on AI making StackExchange feel obsolete while knowledge gets locked up, and caps it with a domain-name cautionary tale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-29.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-28.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/303118891c325ea66b90a1409e3c9a44a16f48d4458d738ed0cb05a1e09852bc.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tipa runs a HeroQuest: First Light dungeon crawl where the Ring of Return exposes a fake “Fire King,” a Witch Hand ambush, and finally summons the real spirit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux shares an EVE Online newbie brain-dump on flying a Caldari Cormorant destroyer, applying SKINs without UI pain, and what the ship’s actually good (and bad) for in PvP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/00a271d2893a22838427a2ae57d461aabec3783c448be225e736a6b9a9d667c3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joar checks in on World of Warcraft’s pre-patch: core alts feel solid (DK/paladin/frost mage favorites), most addons survived, delves are feeding vaults, and FFXIV/ESO/GW2 are on the side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/0c61bfc5074257f94d1bffdb371ca16e89e7f1ebeb9066604fadd4895167e6a6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrew’s Quest 64 week is mostly fields, tougher fights, and leveling, but he reaches Larapool after a weird “boat trip,” with Shannon still popping up at every inn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie finally circles back to Control by replaying it and diving into The Foundation and AWE, praising the Oldest House’s surreal world design and the DLC’s cryptic, creepy pull.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm bumbles from Guild Wars’ Great Northern Wall into Embark Beach, gets overwhelmed by mission options and level 20s, then has to Google how to get back home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/a77cddcecfc61fbf8bf86d890608ebec7f9e53c1914abd9655fbfee615c2fb59.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Juhis, despite hating arbitrary scoring, can’t stop laughing at Taskmaster and crowns UK Series 7 best-in-show, celebrating loophole-friendly tasks and killer cast chemistry with Greg Davies and Alex&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski dunks hard on Starfleet Academy (2026), calling it Gossip Girl Trek with pointless post-Burn setting, hate-fueled character dynamics, and CW vibes—Brit Marling just voices the computer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner ties literal winter storms to a broader social/political/tech tempest, rattling off grim headlines and the feeling we’re stuck in a never-ending streaming-series crisis arc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/29fc0c04f1bcf48ed9f80352e31ee1c11fbd36120ac543395da50e1b81abf7ec.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tobold contrasts reactions to Ashli Babbitt vs Alex Pretti, digs into 2nd Amendment hypocrisy, and argues America can’t keep millions “technically illegal” without crises like Minneapolis protests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer revisits 1998 UserLand posts and argues RSS beats siloed AT Proto/Bluesky for publishing, plus a reminder that “us vs them” thinking isn’t working on the web.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/23f365ef8346c92c3a952d128329e33d9fcb321ad0a9c0be9506df8e985e6a1f.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Wednesday, 28 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aywren rebrands as “Reflections of a Middle-Aged Gamer,” explains why she’s sticking with her current domain, and walks through a cleaner layout, sidebar cuts, and Topics upgrades.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-28.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-27.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/52c6a3573ef85564c66b4372900ae8d740922591b7b1a97ad7db954c1e675fd6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stargrace’s WoW gold log: 4.4 million this week thanks to better sales as Remix ends, mostly pets/transmog/recipes, plus a side quest of spending big on housing collectibles and letting auctions lapse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/305718318fa9d95b36c9ab4688842d179ecf169e19cba681ac7383a018df5a33.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Syp hits level 20 on a TBC Shaman in WoW Classic, raves about Joana’s in-game leveling guide and friendly small-scale community moments, then groans at the marathon water totem quest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger commits to a magic build in Tainted Grail: The Fall of Avalon and is pleasantly surprised it’s not just glass-cannon stuff—spells, cubes, and wands can put out DPS and stay alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/b6b344a1f8da7a7f4a6009dad54db841590eed3dca425afcd89d0e8ebec59e67.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nimgimli finally finishes Clair Obscur: Expedition 33 and loves it—if you play it in focused bursts—because the dodge/parry timing skills get rusty fast, especially across Xbox vs PC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi’s Resident Evil Village write-up is more diary than review, riffing on the Winters’ “post-hell” setup, the dark fairytale framing, and how the game’s vibe lands across chapters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/ce172f29d0012981b5476d99d91c661a35221932480d8e7db51fb262f0d4a5a8.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Krista revisits Pearl Abyss’ DokeV—open-world creature-collecting with Korean folklore flair—and wonders where it went, since the big 2021 reveal still hasn’t turned into a release date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/570da7c314e923477c6d7b24a29e164ef18b31889ea454af28e93b42873858a9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar tests WoW’s new housing endeavours and finds the real problem isn’t “two dailies,” it’s murky UI, diminishing returns, and progress so tiny it feels like you’re pushing a boulder alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm wraps up five No Man’s Sky expeditions, then hits that sandbox whiplash—so many goals (bases, freighters, achievements), but no checklist, plus some base-building quirks and bugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner tracks signs of political wobble amid winter-storm chaos and protests—reports of officials being sidelined, GOP jitters, shutdown stakes—and argues the only play is sustained public pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer uses Darkest Hour’s Churchill moment as a mirror for today: tell the public the truth, stop “clever” debates, and push big systemic fixes like Supreme Court terms and enforcing the 14th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/788233e513c322d2e91a5e119cbf577e6a97417edb89a38e8b7f7d396788c917.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jamie Zawinski’s iPad wants to jump from 18 to 26, and he’s crowdsourcing regret—complete with commenters arguing security updates while he clings proudly to an iOS 15 iPhone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/7ca8850a216c596b9fa7946ac5d978c12a6d9ab6d182767e9f85f99126d85f44.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Tuesday, 27 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicole digs into the 1982 Yamaha MR-10 as a surprisingly late preset-only drum machine, contrasting analog circuit “drums” with sampled realism and spotlighting its performance-first big instrument 버튼&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-27.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026</title>
      <link>https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-26.html</link>
      <description>&lt;img src="/images/ce2af1924f550561fb3c36c94e79843cf0efc307c3d3cbfd247eae17228365e2.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roger breaks down a magic build in Tainted Grail: The Fall of Avalon—spells, cubes, wands, loadouts—arguing it’s surprisingly sturdy DPS rather than the usual glass-cannon caster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/5b2ed3b5023c35b10c285c512688e964cc90d8b5b6dfd2c5bcd79f8e4f661871.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CrazyKinux brain-dumps a newbie-friendly EVE Online guide to the Caldari Cormorant, including how to redeem/apply SKINs and why the ship’s railgun-range role shines in early PvP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/9d67028b17fdd268a3b82c7c25f596b56671ea58ac09f6959d2b0016101b7cf3.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shintar lays out her Star Wars: The Old Republic Total Galactic War Conquest routine—tiered objectives, point expectations, and why she’s still having fun after already “conquering the galaxy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2d8a7584a7be5643c66729013dd2a9abc3763bf8d09973843922d45af4127680.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kimimi keeps a diary-style deep dive into Resident Evil Village, loving the dark fairytale vibes that never quite fully land, and noting the Winters’ Expansion’s new third-person option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d17f082128fe5bc76fb5d9f49d9e48955620dbf56d321c26ebb3a8feb35b8c24.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Belghast and crew wrap part two of their 2025 Games of the Year podcast, chewing through a vote-weighted grab bag from Hades II and Silksong to Dune Awakening and Deltarune Chapters 3–4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/d1e331f812c11d2e1a3b31007c52b91bec2abf799119d66684cfd91372a2c3c9.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellie finally tackles Control’s DLC The Foundation and AWE—after a full replay—digging into the Oldest House’s surreal foundations, The Board’s cryptic nudges, and that signature Remedy creepiness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/472fb1c4f54a70c3cc1930313dcee74cff760048a45a1af6d1749a3e44d79a39.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wilhelm’s TAGN Fantasy Critic League finally posts its first scores, with Mio: Memories in Orbit climbing and Arknights: Endfield landing “mid,” plus a quick rules refresher on no dropping scored игр.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8e31a9e585d04c0a60412ee2e16d7827f1ee91d8ae0d66e46e42a7d80f444af0.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael revisits 1992’s Living Books: Just Grandma and Me, a clicky Little Critter CD-ROM storybook, and argues the charming animations still work—especially now that ScummVM runs it anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/f711373a7def3cbdf854c4a79a33233d56381e4ee1d98e5e3efc79fad2b67393.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anarchae’s week 4 digest mixes Kubuntu woes and Firefox layout weirdness with mystery-fiction reading, Traitors watch notes, podcast shoutout excitement, and a little FFXIV/Raidou/FateGO gaming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/af9a94c77eddf1cf2284b8c43d9193829a594cb1fed7127a9c859a263fba33d5.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warner shares a chilly Sunday link roundup—blogging vs social, codex-over-phone, AI bubble/disinfo worries, democracy doomscrolling, and a very Canadian rant about modern computing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/2315ff1b305947c5ed8226689059198336ccfcafc7122a3ec5e3017a200ac1d6.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Winer riffs on bleak politics, pushes “accept where we are,” jokes they should host games on ChatGPT, and posts a Metacritic-ranked Best Picture nominees list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img src="/images/8041f91993a8a7d16215ca8b5da001cffadf71d1257faec382a7bba9cc4c2561.png" alt="The Daily Blogroll — Monday, 26 January 2026 image"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily writes up a nightmare like a sci‑fi survival-horror game: her Star Wars OC Emi Takori endlessly pursued by a force-fielded, skating General Grievous, complete with HUD alerts and puzzle pressure&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://westkarana.xyz/2026/01/daily-blogroll-2026-01-26.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
